{
    "subject": "resource/Matthew_McDonough",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Mudvayne",
    "human_readable": "Matthew McDonough is associated with Mudvayne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9509138464927673,
            "question": "What role does Matthew McDonough play in Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.870093584060669,
            "question": "Are there any other members in Mudvayne besides Matthew McDonough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6734415292739868,
            "question": "Who is Matthew McDonough?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6554024815559387,
            "question": "With which musical genre is Mudvayne associated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.638190746307373,
            "question": "What band is Matthew McDonough associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4704906940460205,
            "question": "Where is Mudvayne based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40982162952423096,
            "question": "What is the history of Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38012972474098206,
            "question": "Is Matthew McDonough a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3678051233291626,
            "question": "Has Mudvayne achieved commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25660064816474915,
            "question": "Are there any notable albums released by Mudvayne?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matthew McDonough is associated with Mudvayne.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2978_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Mudvayne achieved commercial success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2978_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Matthew McDonough a musician?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2978_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Mudvayne?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2978_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2978_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents contain information that links Matthew McDonough to Mudvayne, such as being the drummer for the band (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2978/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt) or mentioning his work with the band (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2978/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Matthew McDonough's association with Mudvayne, supporting the statement that he is associated with the band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}